{
    "subject": "resource/Dries_van_der_Lof",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfDeath",
    "object": "Enschede, Netherlands",
    "human_readable": "Dries van der Lof died in Enschede, Netherlands.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9198873043060303,
            "question": "Where did Dries van der Lof die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067996740341187,
            "question": "In which country did Dries van der Lof die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8898218870162964,
            "question": "Was Dries van der Lof Dutch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7667182087898254,
            "question": "What is the name of the city where Dries van der Lof died?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7609182596206665,
            "question": "Where was Dries van der Lof from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44533783197402954,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Dries van der Lof's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41987916827201843,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Dries van der Lof's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.392122745513916,
            "question": "Is there any historical significance to Dries van der Lof's passing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37108853459358215,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Dries van der Lof?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2637992203235626,
            "question": "What is known about Dries van der Lof's profession?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dries van der Lof died in Enschede, Netherlands.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1806_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Dries van der Lof?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1806_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any historical significance to Dries van der Lof's passing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1806_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable events associated with Dries van der Lof's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1806_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1806_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Dries van der Lof died on 24 May 1990 in Enschede, which supports the statement that he died in Enschede, Netherlands."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}